text-sms.com 2002-12-09

# Text-SMS - Privacy Policy

**PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY**

**Text-SMS Privacy Policy**

At Text-SMS we respect and take steps to protect your privacy. We strive to make our site a safe environment for everyone who visits and uses Text-SMS services. We are committed to providing you the best possible online service and experience as well as the best products and services. The purpose of this policy statement is to fully share with you:

  * How we use the information
  * With whom we share the information
  * How you can change the information

This policy addresses our practices with respect to our website, but does not address the practices of any website we link to (including the merchants and content providers we link to). This policy is incorporated into, and subject to the terms of, our User Agreement. 

**How We Use Information collected**  
We use information which you provide us to keep track of the Text-SMS services you have signed up to receive. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content and layout. We do this in an attempt to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. We use your email address to contact you regarding administrative notices or latest news from time to time. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. 

**Disclosure of Your Information**  
We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. We do aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. Text-SMS offers features on our site where we will by necessity, need to provide some of your information to the third party offering such services. To the extent that that third party requires your information to enable you to use their service, we will notify you of the specific information that will be provided to such third parties. Before you use the service you should evaluate whether you will accept the terms and conditions of the third party service, and give Text-SMS the right to pass your information on to that third party. In addition, we must comply with court orders, information requests from government agencies and regulators and other legal and regulatory processes that may require the disclosure of your personally-identifiable information.

**Cookies**  
Our site does not use Cookies. However at some stage we may decide to implement Cookies to speed up and personalise your Text-SMS experience. You can choose not to enable your browser to accept cookies however still be able to use the Text-SMS Interface.

**Frequently Asked Questions**  
Will you send advertising messages to my cell phone, without my consent ?  
No, we will not send you unwanted advertising messages. We may initiate a program whereby we send advertising messages to cell phones. However, this will be an opt-in based service. You will decide if, and when you want to receive advertising on your cell phone.

**I am getting spammed on my cell phone. What's happening ?**  
One of the services, provided by Text-SMS, allows visitors and members to send messages to friends, family, colleagues, using the Text-SMS Interface. The Text-SMS Interface conditions of use forbid spamming to cell phone users and several software filters are in place to block spammers. However, we cannot guarantee that no spamming will ever occur. You have the possibility to block your phone from receiving any message from Text-SMS or Text-SMS members by clicking on the 'do-not-disturb' button on the home page.

**Reviewing/Changing Your Information**  
If at any time you would like to change any information in your account, either as a Desktop Client User go and change your personal preferences from the system tray, or as a host client, go to Member Login from the home page. Here you can change or update your information. You must click Change Details to maintain new changes. 

**Limits on Our Abilities**  
Although your privacy is very important to us, due to the existing legal and technical environment, we cannot ensure that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties in ways not described in this policy. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to address or resolve inquiries or problems.

**Questions?**  
We're always happy to answer your questions and listen to your comments.  
By Email: [info@text-sms.com](mailto:info@text-sms.com)

If you have further questions about our privacy policy or its implementation, please contact [info@text-sms.com](mailto:info@text-sms.com)

You acknowledge that acceptance of this privacy policy is a condition to your use of our services and you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions
